<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE rss PUBLIC "-//Netscape Communications//DTD RSS 0.91//EN"
            "http://my.netscape.com/publish/formats/rss-0.91.dtd">
<rss version="0.91">
<channel>
<title>UltraCorps News</title>
<link>http://ultracorps.sjgames.com/news.html</link>
<description>The latest news about UltraCorps.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2020, Steve Jackson Games, Incorporated</copyright>
<item>
<title>New Mega Starts April 15th</title>
<link>http://ultracorps.sjgames.com/news.html#3858</link>
<description>April Showers&lt;br&gt;  24 turns, open now, closes late on the 13th for a chance to make your move before the game starts on April 15th at 8 pm.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Pandemic is currently being lead by Guderian the Great, with Wadd and Dr_Sci in close 2nd and 3rd.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;-- Starcharger, Fleet Admiral</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>March Of Madness Leads To Pandemic</title>
<link>http://ultracorps.sjgames.com/news.html#3857</link>
<description>Breakers and Greyhulk are tied for the lead in March of Madness!  Malmbando is a close 3rd.  Three other players are tied for 4th.  With around a week to go, lots of things can happen.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Pandemic is slated to start on April Fool&#39;s Day, April 1st.  There are about three more days to join if anyone wants to sign up for strategy, diplomacy and battle - not necessarily in that order.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;br&gt;-- Starcharger, Fleet Admiral</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pandemic</title>
<link>http://ultracorps.sjgames.com/news.html#3856</link>
<description>A new UltraCorps mega game, &quot;Pandemic&quot;, is now open for joining! For more info, or to join this game, visit http://ultracorps.sjgames.com/zgame/game/gameinfo.html?gameID=83151 &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The first tick will be April 1st at 8pm, SJ Games time.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;-- Starcharger, Fleet Admiral</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>April Mega Game</title>
<link>http://ultracorps.sjgames.com/news.html#3855</link>
<description>With a lot of the galaxy under lock-down it seems like a good time to run another Mega Game.  It will be a little like the wild west with an assymetrical map and wide spacing.  It should be different and fun.  Feel free to share the Ultracorps.com link around as many people will be looking for things to do as they stay close to home in this global pandemic.  The game will be available for joining in a little less than a week.&lt;br&gt;-- Starcharger, Fleet Admiral</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>March Of Madness</title>
<link>http://ultracorps.sjgames.com/news.html#3854</link>
<description>The March of Madness is upon us! A grueling match of 31 turns, give or take one or two, will end with the victor taking the spoils.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The game is open for joining now and will close on February 29th to new players. The map will be built and populated and commanders will have about two days to make their first move before the first tick on March 2nd at 8 PM Steve Jackson Games time.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Another Mega will start in May, and in each odd numbered month, with a Holiday Ring Game in December.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;br&gt;-- Starcharger, Fleet Admiral</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>March Of Madness!</title>
<link>http://ultracorps.sjgames.com/news.html#3853</link>
<description>A new UltraCorps mega game, &quot;March of Madness&quot;, is now open for joining! For more info, or to join this game, visit http://ultracorps.sjgames.com/zgame/game/gameinfo.html?gameID=83105The first tick has not been scheduled.&lt;br&gt;-- Starcharger, Fleet Admiral</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>March Mega Madness!</title>
<link>http://ultracorps.sjgames.com/news.html#3852</link>
<description>We will open the March Mega for joining on or around February 26th.  The game will close to new players on Leap Day, February 29, in the gloaming time of twilight.  Planets will be generated and home worlds established.  There will be about 48 hours to make your moves before the first tick on Monday March 2nd at 8 PM.  There will be 30 or so turns and the game will wrap up just before or right around April Fool&#39;s Day.&lt;br&gt;-- Starcharger, Fleet Admiral</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Breakers Wins!  Caruso Wins!</title>
<link>http://ultracorps.sjgames.com/news.html#3851</link>
<description>Two players tie for first in a decadent display of firepower and cunning!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Congratulations to Breakers!  Congratulation to Caruso!  Each player get a Badge for being the Winner in a Mega Game!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Placid Platypus gets the bronze ultranium medal for 3rd place!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Gerry.gadget, Starcharger, Russian, Black Knight, ScaryRaven, Dr_Sci and Arillus round out the Top Ten.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;February is an off month.  We will host a 12 player game for those who want to keep their glowing tentacles in the water.  Come back about five days before the Ides of March (February 23rd)and join up to play in the March Mega Madness!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;-- Starcharger, Fleet Admiral</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Decadent Race</title>
<link>http://ultracorps.sjgames.com/news.html#3850</link>
<description>It is a tight cluster at the top with Caruso on top of the mountain looking down and four commanders all within one or two planets of 1st place looking up.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There is an ominous lull with only 5 battles, one of those being a bloodless takeover of an undefended planet, and another an auto-fleet returning to a now hostile administration.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;40% of the game remains and The Acutron is picking up satellite chatter that indicates the battles will soon be roaring and the decadent 20&#39;s will indeed start out with a truly Deca Dance!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;br&gt;-- Starcharger, Fleet Admiral</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sun_Tzu Wins!</title>
<link>http://ultracorps.sjgames.com/news.html#3849</link>
<description>Hail Mighty Commander Sun_Tzu!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Well met!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You have won the opportunity to name a world in the name of your choice, within Acutronical reason!As we move forward into the new decade, one wonders can Sun_Tzu or Undead Bones win again in this new world order?We will see if skill and strategy will win over against the wishes of the masses!&lt;br&gt;-- Starcharger, Fleet Admiral</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
